bonziteam.com 2016-03-13

# Bonzi General Privacy Policy - Bonzi - Sports Management and online registration made easy

## Bonzi General Privacy Policy

_Revised 5/14/2014  _

At Bonzi Technology, Inc. (“Bonzi”, “We”, “Us”) we take your privacy seriously and are committed to bringing you a quality product and experience while protecting your privacy when using the Bonzi product provided for your use by your organization. (“Site”).  This Privacy Policy is also part of our Terms of Use which you can view at http://www.gobonzi.com/terms-of-use.

The following terms have the following meanings:

**“User or Member”** includes members or persons 13 years of age or older, however if you are under the age of 18, or if your child is under the age of 18, please review our Children’s Privacy Policy located at http://www.gobonzi.com/childrens-privacy-policy.

**“Personal information”** means individually identifiable information about an individual that is collected online, such as first and last name, a home address, an e-mail address, a telephone number or any information collected from an individual and combined with such identifying information.

“ **Organization** ” means the organization with whom you are a member or intend to apply for membership by registering online or authorizing the organization to enter your information into their Site and Bonzi product.  The Organization has elected to use and/or purchased Bonzi products to operate their Site to run its operation and offer services to members.

**“Site”** means a web site, online registration, or other service provided by Bonzi which your Organization has purchased or elected to use and through which offers services to its Members.

**Scope of this Policy**  
This Policy describes how we collect, use and disclose personal information about our Users who use Bonzi products and its services and applications. This policy incorporates by reference the Terms of Use (“Terms”) for the Site and those Terms apply to this Policy. View our Terms of Use using the link provided below.

NOTE: For those Users who are 13 years of age and over but under 18 years of age, or for parents of users who are 13 years of age and over but under 18 years of age, please  view our Children’s Privacy Policy using the link provided below, which applies to the information we collect those Users. Before using this Site, please read the Terms of Use.

  * View our Terms of Use at [http://www.gobonzi.com/terms-of-use](http://www.bonzicentral.com/terms-of-use/)
  * View our Children’s Privacy Policy at [http://www.gobonzi.com/childrens-privacy-policy](http://www.bonzicentral.com/childrens-privacy-policy/)

**BY USING OR ACCESSING OUR SERVICES, OR BY PERMITTING YOUR CHILD TO USE OR ACCESS OUR SERVICES, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS POLICY.**

**About Us**  
Bonzi Technology, Inc. (dba Bonzi Sports Software) (“Bonzi”  “we,” or “our”) provides the product that operates the website (the “Site”) purchased by your Organization, including any social networking service, Web page, platform, or application offered through the Site. We at Bonzi are dedicated to safeguarding your privacy.

We offer Users through the Site access to services such as the ability to register online providing your personal information for participation in your Organization’s programs, use of the Organization’s web site, receive communication from your Organization, be assigned to a team, and share and receive information with others on your team including a coach for your team.  Information provided by you to your Organization is owned by your Organization as outlined under our Service Agreement with your Organization.

Only authorized administrators of the Organization may view and manage the information you provided to them for participation in their programs. Bonzi staff members may view your information in support of the Organization administrators.  Your Organization owns the data entered into their Bonzi product and the Site. Your Organization, at their sole discretion, may choose to share your information as they deem necessary to run their operation. Examples of this may be team rosters with your information provided to coaches, information provided to procure insurance coverage, or information that creates a membership on your behalf with a parent organization to ensure your participation and access to programs provided by your Organization.

Members (for example: coaches, referees, participants, players and parents) who registered with their Organization may have access to use, but not limited to, the following services in the Bonzi product and the Site:

  * Create a member account including personal information such as name, address, phone number, email address, and birth date.
  * Add family members to your account with the same personal information.
  * Register online
  * Receive notification of game schedules and schedule updates
  * Receive email communication from their Organization
  * Receive notifications via text message or personal email (optional)
  * Post a profile with photo
  * Make payments online
  * View balances owed
  * Print medical release and other forms

**Information We Collect From You and How We Collect It**

**Information We Collect Directly**  
When you create your account, you will be asked for your first name, last name, user ID and a password. We may also request additional optional information about you such as date of birth, email address, other contact information, or nickname for example. We may also ask you for information relating to your preferences however, such information is optional. We will only require information that is reasonably necessary for your successful use of the Site.

**Information We Collect Passively**  
We may also passively collect information on site usage patterns or through content that members post on our message boards or by comments. For example, we may collect certain non-personal information from all visitors to our site, such as IP address, the date and time of visit, time spent on the site, the type of browser used (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system used (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), the ISP from which the visitor receives Internet access, and aggregate information regarding what pages users of the site access or visit. This information may be combined with the personal information we collect from users.  
Bonzi uses Cookies to track the your session on the Site or to make your use of the Site more convenient by storing certain pieces of data.  A Cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to store on a web browser so it can later be read back from that browser. You can easily delete Cookies from your computer by following instructions provided in the Help guide for your browser. If you choose to disable Cookies, the Site may not work properly during use.

**Content Posted to or Sent Through Site** _  
_ Although Users on our Site may be allowed by their Organization to communicate only with teammates in a “closed” environment (only with their teammates), it’s important to note that by their very nature email accounts, message boards, and other interactive / social networking services disclose information, including personal information you’ve entered to others on your team. We do not review any content before it is posted and cannot guarantee that we will find and remove inappropriate content that has been posted to our Site. We look to each team and its members to use the Site appropriately and in accordance with our Terms of Use.

**Tracking Activities on the Site**  
When you are logged into your account, we may track your activities within the Site. For example, we track the pages visited, the length of time spent logged in, the information submitted about preferences and comments posted on the team’s dashboards. This information is associated with your Bonzi username and may be combined with the personally identifiable information we collect from you.

We may partner with third parties to provide content and/or to display targeted advertisements. We will not share your personally identifiable information with these third parties. However, some of these third parties may use tracking technologies, such as cookies and Web beacons, on our Site in order to track user activity. We do not exercise control over or have access to these tracking technologies or the information practices of these parties, which are subject to the privacy policies of these third parties.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**  
We may use the personal information that we collect from a you to determine whether you are eligible to use the Site, to obtain consent from you to use the service, to provide an interactive online experience, to respond to requests for assistance in the use of the software product, to send newsletters, and to provide content that we believe that you may be interested in. In addition, we may use some of the information we collect about you to display to you targeted advertising or other content that we think may be of interest or value.

We may use non-personal information such as information about the pages visited to improve the design, content and performance of our site, or to analyze site usage and the popularity of certain pages of the Site.

We may also match the non-personal information we collect from you (such as pages visited) with the personal information (such as the member’s name and age or other account information) in our database. Such combined information is kept in our internal database under the member’s user name.

**How We Share a Your Personal Information with Third Parties**  
We will not sell, rent or trade your personal information. We may disclose the personal information we obtain from you to our affiliates; however, if we do so the affiliate’s use and disclosure of the personal information will be subject to restrictions at least as strict as those contained in this Policy. We may also disclose such information to our third party vendors who may generate content, provide customer service or billing services, and/or monitor or manage interactive features available on our website. These third parties have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of personal information, and the information is not shared with any of these third parties for their own marketing purposes.

In addition, the information collected from you as part of your profile information, such as name and age, is shared with your Organization administrator, teammates, coaches and where applicable, other parents connected to the team. All of the information provided by a you is always visible to you. You can disable, delete or modify any of your information by logging in and accessing your profile. For more information on how to do this, see the section below entitled “How To Review, Delete or Alter the Information Collected From You.”

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response legal process – for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose such information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our Terms or this Policy, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer personal information if we are acquired by or merged with another company or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding.

**Aggregate and Anonymized Information**  
We may also share aggregate or anonymized information about you with non-affiliated third parties for advertising, marketing or research purposes. For example, we may share demographic information about users with our marketing partners and third party advertisers, which may be used to determine what types of advertising content to display to Site users. However, we will never share your personally identifiable information with any third parties for marketing, advertising or research purposes.

**How To Review, Delete or Alter the Information Collected From Your Child**  
You can review your personal information at any time by logging into their profile. You may also be able to have your personal information completely deleted by contacting your Organization.

**Data Security**  
We have implemented commercially reasonable safeguards to protect personal information that we collect and store. Despite these precautions, however, no data security safeguards are foolproof. Unauthorized individuals may find ways to obtain personal information from or to access the Site. Please keep in mind that we cannot and do not guarantee that content posted at the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. Any content that you post is at your own risk.

**Third Party Links**  
At times, our website may contain links to other third party websites. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Policy but, instead, is governed by the privacy policies of those third party websites. Bonzi is not responsible for your access to and use of such third party websites.

**Changes to this General Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to amend this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. We will post a notice on this website if and when this policy changes to alert users that a new policy is in place. If we intend to use or disclose your personal information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email.

**Contact Us**  
If you have questions, comments or concerns about any of our privacy policies or practices, or to raise any other issue related to privacy, you may contact Bonzi at:

8100 SW Nyberg St. Suite 450  
Tualatin, Oregon  97062
